Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Photographs PHOTOS 019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: New York Teacher Photograph Files, 1951-1987.
  - Subseries I:A: United Federation of Teachers.
    - Sub-subseries I:A:6: Schools and Students
      - Sub-sub-subseries I:A:6a: Elementary Schools
        - PS 70 Bronx, Drugs Symposium, Apr 21, 1971 (Item 1457)
        - PS 70 Queens, Demonstration, Feb 4, 1972 (Item 1893)
        - PS 72 Bronx, Spring Clean-Up Campaign, Mar 1971 (Item 1425)
        - PS 72 Bronx, Culture Fair, Jun 7, 1972 (Item 1820)
        - PS 75 Bronx Visiting PS 72 Bronx, May 5, 1971 (Item 1590)
        - PS 75 Bronx, Black History Week, 1972 (Item 1835)
        - PS 75 Brooklyn, Puro Belpre Childrens Caravan, Jun 1972 (Item 1817)
        - PS 75 Brooklyn, Pan American Day, Jun 11, 1972 (Item 1865)
        - Biaggi, Mario at PS 76 Bronx, Italian Earthquake Fund by student, undated (Item 3268)
        - PS 77 Bronx, Jan 20, 1972 (Item 1719)
        - PS 78 Bronx, Martin Luther King Jr. Day Celebration, Jan 1971 (Item 1289)
        - PS 81 Bronx, Kern's class visiting Bronx Boro President Stanley Simon, undated (Item 5332)
        - Robert J. Christen School, used to be PS 81 Bronx, undated (Item 5332)
        - PS 83 Manhattan, Performance, Apr 1974 (Item 3005)
        - PS 83 Bronx, Special Olympics, undated (Item 5514)
        - PS 84 Brooklyn Primary Program, undated (Item 1883)
        - PS 85 Street Blocking Demonstration, Oct 22, 1971 (Item 1936)
        - PS 85 Exhibit, undated (Item 1196)
        - PS 86 Queens Fence Protest, Nov 1971 (Item 1933)
        - PS 87 Manhattan, undated (Item 5811)
        - PS 90 Brooklyn, Hoop Dance Demonstration, Apr 29, 1971 (Item 1502)
        - PS 90 Bronx Aerospace Project, Feb 6, 1972 (Item 1892)
        - PS 90 Bronx, renamed George Meany School, Ceremony, Sep 1981 (Item 1892)
        - PS 91 Brooklyn, Opening of Mini-School, Jul 1973 (Item 1074)
        - Special Arts Festival, PS 91 Queens, Jun 1979 (Item 4466)
        - PS 91 Queens, Aug 1985 (Item 5661)
        - PS 92 Brooklyn, Sep 1981 (Item 5475)
        - Parents and teachers join forces at PS 92, undated (Item 195)
        - PS 92 photos, undated (Item 195)
        - PS 94 Brooklyn, Weinman speaks to chapter, Feb 1982 (Item 5334)
        - PS 94 Bronx, Play, Wizard of Oz, undated (Item 1816)
        - PS 94 Brooklyn, teacher C.E. Cunningham w/ class, undated (Item 5334)
        - PS 94 Brooklyn, Ed Muir w/ members, undated (Item 5334)
        - PS 95 Queens, Christmas Toy Drive, 1981 (Item 5500)
        - PS 98 Queens, undated (Item 5794)
        - PS 99 Brooklyn, Woodwork shop on Assembly Line techniques, Jun 1971 (Item 1627)
        - Postcard from student from PS 100 Manhattan, undated (Item 168)
        - Dial-A-Teacher, PS 102, Bronx, May 1981 (Item 1151)
        - PS 102 Bronx, undated (Item 5686)
        - PS 104 Bronx, Opening of Annex, May 1971 (Item 1565)
        - PS 105 Brooklyn, garden planted by students, undated (Item 5333)
        - PS 107 Manhattan, Christmas Choral Group singing Christmas Carols at City Hall, Dec 1971 (Item 1875)
        - PS 107 Brooklyn, Teachers and Students, Dec 1981 (Item 1839)
        - PS 108 Manhattan, Art Show, Nov 12, 1972 (Item 2080)
        - PS 108 Manhattan, Prepare art work for Gimbels East exhibit, undated (Item 2023)
        - PS 109 Manhattan, "Teacher Party for Parents", undated (Item 2252)
        - PS 110 Bronx, Gym Class (MES), undated (Item 575)
        - PS 114 Bronx, Puerto Rican Discovery Day, Nov 1971 (Item 1640)
        - Puerto Rico Discovery Day Programs, PS 115, Puerto Rican Heritage Week, UFT, Nov 1980 (Item 2051)
        - PS 116 Brooklyn, Health Fair, May 28, 1971 (Item 1554)
        - PS 116 Manhattan, Black History Week, undated (Item 5392)
        - Hevesi, Alan (Assemblyman) speaking at PS 119 Bronx, Apr 1974 (Item 2997)
        - Crowning Queen, PS 120 Brooklyn, Jun 13, 1970 (Item 1061)
        - PS 120 Brooklyn, Humane Education, May 1981 (Item 5407)
        - PS 120 Brooklyn, Humane Education (poster shot of child and teacher), Feb 1982 (Item 5407)
        - PS 120 Coronation, undated (Item 1364)
        - PS 122 Brooklyn, Science Fair, May 1971 (Item 1474)
        - District 1, PS 122, COPE Meeting, Mar 1973 (Item 2324)
        - PS 122 Brooklyn, Parents demonstrate for funds needed to complete a new primary school, Apr 1976 (Item 4171)
        - PS 122 Brooklyn seeks new building, undated (Item 201)
        - PS 123, Classroom photos, Apr 11, 1969 (Item 1368)
        - PS 124 Manhattan, 1981 Water Crisis, Mayor Koch (Item 5346)
        - PS 124 Brooklyn, Teachers' Recognition Day Luncheon, undated (Item 4578)
        - PS 125 Queens, Students, undated (Item 5150)
        - PS 125 Queens, undated (Item 5150)
        - PS 126 Manhattan, Apr 8, 1970 (Item 1378)
        - Highbridge House and PS 126 combination, undated (Item 535)
        - PS 127 Queens, Martin Luther King Jr. Celebration, Jan 1971 (Item 1404)
        - PS 127 Queens, Martin Luther King Day Celebration, Jan 18, 1972 (Item 1717)
        - King, Martin Luther, Jr., film premiere held at PS 128 Manhattan, May 22, 1971 (Item 1536)
        - PS 128 Manhattan, Dominican Independence Day, Mar 1980 (Item 1171)
        - PS 128 Manhattan, Japanese-American Art Contest, Sep 1980 (Item 1171)
        - PS 128 Brooklyn, Drug Program, 2/25, undated (Item 2205)
        - PS 129 Manhattan, Afro-American History Exhibit, Feb 1968 (Item 375)
        - PS 129 Manhattan, Parent Participation Program, Mar 1981 (Item 375)
        - PS 129 Manhattan, Dial-A-Teacher, Jan 1982 (Item 375)
        - Dial-A-Teacher, PS 129 Manhattan, Jan 1982 (Item 1151)
        - PS 129 Manhattan, at Teacher's Store, Jan 1982 (Item 375)
        - PS 130, Teacher Self-Evaluation Program, Apr 7, 1970 (Item 1323)
        - Chinese New Year, PS 130, Jan 26, 1971 (Item 1369)
        - PS 130 Manhattan, Chinese-Puerto Rican Day, Apr 30, 1971 (Item 1469)
        - PS 130 Bronx, Reading Class, May 17, 1971 (Item 1539)
        - PS 130 Manhattan, Pan American Day, Jun 4, 1972 (Item 1833)
        - PS 130 Manhattan "Chinese New Year", Feb 1973 (Item 2184)
        - PS 130 Bronx, Culture Fair, Cultural Arts Week, Jun 1980 (Item 1813)
        - PS 130 Brooklyn, undated (Item 5123)
        - Science Safari Program at PS 132 Brooklyn, Summer 1970 (Item 1044)
        - PS 133 Bronx, Aerospace Program, undated (Item 2060)
        - Dedication of Mini-School, PS 134 Queens, 1970 (Item 1043)
        - Loeb, Esther (PS 134 Manhattan), undated (Item 5623)
        - PS 135 Brooklyn, undated (Item 5756)
        - PS 136 Bronx, Performing Play, May 27, 1971 (Item 1538)
        - Puerto Rican Discovery Day, PS 137, Nov 19, 1970 (Item 1320)
        - PS 137 Chapter Consultation Committee Meeting, undated (Item 4633)
        - PS 138 Queens, Student Council term project, Friendship boxes for needy children, May 1971 (Item 1507)
        - Parents of PS 138 Brooklyn picket for MES, undated (Item 200)
        - PS 138 Boycott of Board Of Ed, undated (Item 517)
        - PS 140 Brooklyn, Gates Program at School, Abe Levine, Jan 1982 (Item 5508)
        - Buzz Session, PS 142, undated (Item 1119)
        - PS 144 Brooklyn, Fashion Show, undated (Item 1828)
        - PS 145 Brooklyn, International Luncheon, Apr 1971 (Item 1568)
        - PS 145 Brooklyn, Parents visit school, Mar 1981 (Item 2636)
        - PS 145 Brooklyn, Naming of school in honor of Roberto Clemente, undated (Item 2636)
        - Puerto Rican Discovery Day, PS 146, Nov 1970 (Item 1325)
        - PS 146 Bronx, Nov 30, 1970 (Item 1264)
        - PS 147 Queens, One-day school boycott, Feb 8, 1971 (Item 1482)
        - PS 148 Brooklyn, Science Fair (Class 5-2g), Feb 1971 (Item 1481)
        - Puerto Rican Discovery Day, PS 150, Nov 19, 1970 (Item 1322)
        - PS 150 Bronx, Black and Puerto Rican Culture Exhibit, May 5, 1971 (Item 1471)
        - Parent Participation Program, PS 150 Queens: Betty Holmes and Assemblyman John Flack, undated (Item 5328)
        - Gudiance, Special Ed, PS 150 Queens, undated (Item 5127)
        - PS 151 Brooklyn, American-Puerto Rican Festival, 1970 (Item 1388)
        - PS 151 Brooklyn, Dec 16, 1970 (Item 1388)
        - PS 151 Manhattan, Feb 1980 (Item 5223)
        - PS 151 Brooklyn, Dial-a-Teacher, Mar 1981 (Item 1388)
        - PS 151 Brooklyn, Dial-a-Teacher, Apr 1981 (Item 1388)
        - PS 155 Brooklyn, Special Science Show, Jun 1981 (Item 5462)
        - PS 155 Brooklyn, School Improvement Plan, Jun 1981 (Item 5462)
        - School Conditions, PS 156 Brooklyn, undated (Item 487)
        - PS 157 Bronx, Negro History Week, 2/14-18/72, Feb 14, 1972 (Item 1834)
        - PS 157 Brooklyn, undated (Item 5223)
        - PS 158 Manhattan, Play, "Lovers and Other Strangers", May 1971 (Item 1515)
        - Guidance Counselors, PS 158, Jun 1979 (Item 3676)
        - PS 158 Manhattan, Spring Festival, 1982 (Item 1515)
        - PS 159 Brooklyn Celebrates Black History Week, 1971 (Item 1441)
        - PS 160 Bronx, 1980 (Item 5336)
        - PS 160 Queens, Clifton Webber and Albert Kisseloff, undated (Item 149)
        - PS 161 Manhattan, Tenth Anniversary Celebration, Jun 17, 1972 (Item 1925)
        - PS 161 Brooklyn, Octoberfest 1981 (Item 5223)
        - Bilingual Education Conference PS 163 Manhattan, 1970 (Item 1116)
        - PS 163 Manhattan, class size problems (Astrowsky, Dist. 3 representative), 1980 (Item 5312)
        - PS 163 Queens, Career Education Day [Includes but may not be limited to:] Silver, Bernard, Mar 1982 (Item 5526)
        - PS 165 Manhattan being visited by Puerto Rican Teachers Delegation, Feb 26, 1971 (Item 1402)
        - PS 167 Brooklyn Demonstration, Sep 28, 1970 (Item 1268)
        - PS 167 Brooklyn, Table Demonstration, May 10, 1971 (Item 1501)
        - PS 167 Brooklyn, Sickle Cell Anemia Testing Program, May 17, 1972 (Item 1854)
        - PS 168 Brooklyn Science Fair, Mar 1971 (Item 1428)
        - Transitional Classes, PS 169 Brooklyn, Feb 1980 (Item 5015)
        - PS 169 Brooklyn, 65th Anniversary, Jun 1981 (Item 5015)
        - PS 169 Brooklyn, Parent Participation Program, undated (Item 5015)
        - Dial-A-Drill, PS 171, undated (Item 1151)
        - PS 174, Opera, "Aida", Dec 1971 (Item 1932)
        - PS 175 Brooklyn, students attend University of RI Basketball clinic, Aug 1972 (Item 2035)
        - PS 177 Brooklyn, with Irving Anker, Mar 1977 (Item 4153)
        - PS 178 Queens, building shot, Dec 1967 (Item 336)
        - PS 178 Queens, District 26 Multi Media Center, Feb 4, 1973 (Item 2190)
        - PS 178 Queens, Hygiene Class, undated (Item 336)
        - PS 178 Queens, Street opposite 178, undated (Item 336)
        - Hill, Velma, visiting PS 179 Queens, Jan 18, 1972 (Item 1715)
        - PS 179 Manhattan, Class size problems and discussions, Oct 1980 (Item 2855)
        - PS 179 Brooklyn, retirement of Dr. George J. Hoffman, Jan 1981 (Item 5348)
        - PS 179 Manhattan, Demonstration (contact sheet), undated (Item 2855)
        - PS 183 Queens, Airline stewardesses give gifts to children at Christmas, Dec 1972 (Item 2448)
        - PS 183 Manhattan, Fair, undated (Item 1849)
        - PS 185 Manhattan, Open House, Jun 1975 (Item 3846)
        - PS 185 Brooklyn, Museum in a school, May 1982 (Item 5556)
        - PS 186 (District 6), City Hall Demonstration, Feb 24, 1971 (Item 1396)
        - PS 186 (District 6) 135 St. and Broadway, Demonstration, Feb 24, 1971 (Item 1397)
        - PS 186 Brooklyn, Art Fair, Jun 1973 (Item 2642)
        - PS 186 Manhattan, Press Conference, undated (Item 1825)
        - PS 187 Manhattan, Clean-Up Campaign, Nov 11, 1973 (Item 2748)
        - Sight Course, PS 188, Apr 28, 1970 (Item 1153)
        - CLIMB Music Program, Dist. 21, PS 188 Brooklyn, Mar 30, 1971 (Item 1436)
        - Parent Participation Program, PS 188 Manhattan, Nov 1980 (Item 5328)
        - PS 189 Brooklyn, Joseph Califano, undated (Item 2220)
        - PS 189 Brooklyn, "Clothing Drive," classroom scene (negatives), undated (Item 2220)
        - PS 189 Brooklyn, Beatrice Vitanya, undated (Item 2220)
        - PS 189 Brooklyn, Lois Rosen, undated (Item 2220)
        - PS 189 Brooklyn, Sylvester Leaks, undated (Item 2220)
        - PS 190 Manhattan, Road to Innovation Program, Dec 19, 1971 (Item 1638)
        - PS 191 Brooklyn, opening of, undated (Item 4577)
        - PS 193 Queens, Parent Outreach program, Holmes, Apr 1981 (Item 4287)
        - PS 193 Queens, June Graduation Ceremony, Abe Levine speaks, undated (Item 4287)
        - PS 193 Queens, La Guardia Aerospace Mural, undated (Item 4287)
        - PS 193 Queens, Parent Participation Program, undated (Item 4287)
        - PS 194 Manhattan, Demonstration at District Office, undated (Item 1564)
        - PS 196 Brooklyn, Teacher-Mom Program, Mar 3, 1971 (Item 1409)
        - PS 196 Brooklyn, Art Exhibit, May 1971 (Item 1520)
        - PS 203 Queens, Corrective Reading Program, Jun 1973 (Item 2628)
        - PS 203 Queens, School Improvement Plan Comm., Dec 1980 (Item 2628)
        - PS 203 Queens, Sorrentino and Carr, Dec 1980 (Item 2628)
        - PS 205 Queens, students and teachers, Sep 1981 (Item 5461)
        - PS 205 Brooklyn, Mary Rose DeMattia, filming book, May 1982 (Item 1333)
        - PS 206 Brooklyn, UFT Chapter Meeting, Apr 22, 1971 (Item 1465)
        - Tree Planting Dedication, PS 207 Brooklyn, Jun 1970 (Item 1065)
        - PS 208 Brooklyn, Martin Luther King Jr. Assembly and Discussion Panel, Jan 14, 1971 (Item 1390)
        - PS 208, Operation Adoption brings girl to NYC, undated (Item 2516)
        - PS 208, Adopted child and family, undated (Item 2030)
        - PS 208 Brooklyn, Social Science symposium, Alice Marsh speaker, undated (Item 2064)
        - District 21, PS 209 Brooklyn, Naming Ceremonies, Jun 1979 (Item 2208)
        - PS 213 Queens, first graders with computer (PET), undated (Item 5546)
        - PS 214 Queens, Parents Boycott, Sep 14, 1970 (Item 1367)
        - PS 214 Brooklyn, Dance and Art Festival, Jun 5, 1972 (Item 1822)
        - Painter's Union picket line at PS 214 Queens, undated (Item 1917)
        - PS 215 Queens, Jun 1975 (Item 3741)
        - Free to Be... PS 215 Brooklyn, Song, "Sisters and Brothers", undated (Item 1885)
        - PS 215 Brooklyn, Dedication Program, undated (Item 1885)
        - PS 219 Annex, Christmas Party, Dec 23, 1971 (Item 1890)
        - PS 219, undated (Item 1376)
        - PS 220 Queens, undated (Item 5223)
        - PS 221, Play, Hamlet, Jun 23, 1971 (Item 1845)
        - PS 221 Brooklyn, Play, The King and I, May 19, 1972 (Item 1821)
        - PS 222 Brooklyn, British Festival, Jun 1976 (Item 4429)
        - PS 225 Brooklyn, "Dig," Raymond Sostri and his rock fossil, Jan 1971 (Item 1292)
        - PS 225 Brooklyn Music Festival, held at Wm. E. Grady Vocational HS, Mar 1971 (Item 1430)
        - PS 225 Brooklyn, Happening, Apr 1971 (Item 1453)
        - PS 226 Manhattan, Fair sponsored by the Association for Mentally Retarded Children, May 18, 1971 (Item 1545)
        - PS 226 Production of Peter Pan, May 1973 (Item 2527)
        - PS 226 Brooklyn, Olympics Fund Raising Luncheon, May 1973 (Item 2457)
        - PS 226 Brooklyn, Ceremonies, Nov 1979 (Item 2457)
        - PS 226 Brooklyn, Quality of Life Institute, May 1982 (Item 2457)
        - PS 232 Queens, presentation of money collected by trick-or-treating for UNICEF ($939.91), Nov 1971 (Item 1626)
        - Rikers Island School, PS 233 Queens, graduation ceremonies, Jun 1981 (Item 5451)
        - PS 234 Manhattan, teachers and students, Feb 1982 (Item 5524)
        - PS 238 Brooklyn, "Craft-O-Rama", May 1973 (Item 2524)
        - PS 238 Brooklyn, International Day 1980 (Item 2524)
        - PS 238 Brooklyn, Golden Anniversary, May 1981 (Item 2524)
        - PS 241 Brooklyn, Staci-Jo Bruce winner in UFT Labor history essay contest, Feb 14, 1982 (Item 5532)
        - PS 244 Brooklyn, Art Show, undated (Item 1688)
        - PS 249 Brooklyn, Science Fair, 1972 (Item 2136)
        - PS 249 Brooklyn, Students launch balloon highlighting Science Week, Jun 1973 (Item 2641)
        - Zivick, Bernard, PS 249 Brooklyn, at rally, undated (Item 5631)
        - Mock Election, PS 249 Bronx, undated (Item 2029)
        - PS 249 Bronx, Mock Election 20/26/72, undated (Item 2083)
        - PS 255 Brooklyn, Production of Fiddler on the Roof, Jun 1973 (Item 2575)
        - PS 255 Brooklyn, Neighborhood Stabilization, 1979 (Item 2575)
        - Kinzer, Grace, with Chapter Chairman from PS 256 Brooklyn and student, Sep 1974 (Item 3299)
        - PS 257 Brooklyn, Conservation Day (tree planting) Ceremony, May 1971 (Item 1475)
        - PS 261 Brooklyn, Batik Craftswoman Nancy Cogen tries to show the children how to do it, May 1981 (Item 2437)
        - PS 262 Brooklyn Demonstration, Feb 24, 1971 (Item 1399)
        - "Camelot" PS 270 Brooklyn, Jun 19, 1970 (Item 1073)
        - PS 270 Brooklyn, Presentation of books, Jun 1975 (Item 3291)
        - Mini School Demonstration, PS 274 Brooklyn, Jun 17, 1970 (Item 1059)
        - PS 274 Brooklyn, Puerto Rican Discovery Day, Nov 1971 (Item 1628)
        - PS 274 Brooklyn, Production of Fiddler on the Roof, Jun 1973 (Item 2668)
        - PS 274 Brooklyn, Benefit for Rosa Weatherless, May 1980 (Item 1628)
        - PS 284 Brooklyn, Kindergarten Reading Program, Feb 8, 1971 (Item 1313)
        - PS 284 Brooklyn & IS 318 Brooklyn Joint Reading Institute, Apr 1971 (Item 1741)
        - PS 284 Brooklyn, Health Fair, May 27, 1971 (Item 1897)
        - PS 284 Brooklyn, School-Community Health Fair, Jun 1971 (Item 1747)
        - PS 284 Brooklyn, Black History Program, Feb 1972 (Item 1929)
        - PS 284 Brooklyn, Dist. 23 Championship, May 1973 (Item 2553)
        - PS 286 Brooklyn, Ecology Project, 1974 (Item 3123)
        - PS 287 Brooklyn, Reborn as a More Effective School, Mar 1971 (Item 1495)
        - PS 289 Christmas Program, undated (Item 2447)
        - PS 297 Brooklyn, Bye Bye Birdie, Class 5-6, Apr 1971 (Item 1451)
        - PS 297 Brooklyn, Puerto Rican Discovery Day, Nov 1971 (Item 1451)
        - PS 297 Brooklyn, Graduation Ceremony, Jun 25, 1972 (Item 1451)
        - PS 297 Brooklyn, Play, Music Man, undated (Item 1451)
        - PS 299 Brooklyn, Greeting Cards to American Hostages in Iran, Mar 1980 (Item 5223)
        - PS 299 Brooklyn, Honors Mothers, May 1980 (Item 5223)
        - Mann, David PS 299, Brooklyn, undated (Item 5627)
        - Dial-A-Teacher, PS 299 Brooklyn, undated (Item 1151)
        - PS 304 Brooklyn, Picnic and Display, Feb 11, 1970 (Item 1363)
        - PS 304 Brooklyn, Feb 13, 1972 (Item 1778)
        - PS 304 Brooklyn, Carnival, Dec 19, 1972 (Item 2169)
        - PS 304 Brooklyn, PTA, Nov 1980 (Item 2169)
        - PS 304 Brooklyn, Demonstration in support of District 9, undated (Item 1884)
        - PS 304 Brooklyn [Includes but may not be limited to:] Brown, Mary; Lopez, Elsie; Firestone, Al; Torres, Grisell; Britton, Barbara; Perez, Auria, undated (Item 2169)
        - PS 305 Brooklyn, Ossie Davis' Visit, Jan 21, 1972 (Item 1858)
        - Earth Day, PS 307, Apr 22, 1970 (Item 1120)
        - PS 307 Brooklyn, American Dance Center Program, Jan 21, 1972 (Item 1720)
        - PS 321 Brooklyn, Demonstration, 1979 (Item 518)
        - PS 321 Brooklyn, Pan American Week, Mar 1979 (Item 518)
        - PS 321 Brooklyn, Honor Legislators, Mar 1980 (Item 518)
        - PS 321 Brooklyn, International Dinner, Jan 1981 (Item 518)
        - PS 321 Brooklyn, M. O. Akinabe, Nigerian Labor Leader, Visits PS 321, Mar 1981 (Item 518)
        - PS 321 Brooklyn, Discusses Title I aid, May 1982 (Item 518)
        - PS 327 Brooklyn and PS 396, Open House, May 1971 (Item 1361)
        - PS 327 Brooklyn, Scholarship Award Winners, Jun 27, 1972 (Item 1361)
        - Puerto Rican Discovery Day, PS 332, Nov 18, 1970 (Item 1321)
        - PS 332 Brooklyn, Black Music Through the Years, Feb 8, 1971 (Item 1312)
        - PS 332 Brooklyn, First Anniversary of sit, undated (Item 4369)
        - PS 335 Brooklyn, Christmas Talent Show, Dec 21, 1970 (Item 1386)
        - PS 370 Brooklyn, 1978 (Item 4822)
        - PS 371 Brooklyn, Jun 18, 1972 (Item 1814)
        - PS 380 Brooklyn, Budget Cuts and TTC, May 1981 (Item 5415)
        - PS 396 Brooklyn, Fiesta Pan-Americana, Apr 6, 1971 (Item 1571)
        - PS 397 Brooklyn, undated (Item 5338)
        - Teacher Centers, PS 398 Brooklyn, PS 14 Queens, PS 261 Bronx, Jun 1979 (Item 4826)
        - Teacher Centers, PS 398 Brooklyn, 1981 (Item 4826)
      - Sub-sub-subseries I:A:6b: Intermediate and Junior High Schools
        - IS 8 Queens, early school session, undated (Item 2362)
        - IS 10, handing out "lost checks", Jan 14, 1971 (Item 1391)
        - IS 10, "The Brock Peters Auditorium," dedication, May 19, 1972 (Item 1818)
        - Inspection Committee, IS 25 Queens, 1970 (Item 1257)
        - IS 29, Apr 1974 (Item 3007)
        - IS 29 Manhattan Fashion Show, undated (Item 2142)
        - IS 31, visits with Al Shanker, undated (Item 4092)
        - IS 38 Bronx, students receiving "Drug Abuse: Dead End" buttons, part of WNYE-FM drug abuse program, Jan 1971 (Item 1522)
        - IS 49 Brooklyn, undated (Item 5764)
        - UFT Political Action, IS 61 Queens, Jun 1979 (Item 4995)
        - IS 61 Queens, Dec 1979 (Item 803)
        - IS 61 Queens, Chess Club, Aug 1980 (Item 803)
        - IS 61 Queens, undated (Item 5223)
        - IS 70 Manhattan, undated (Item 4907)
        - IS 80 Bronx, Drug Abuse Program, Apr 19, 1971 (Item 1472)
        - IS 87 Manhattan, undated (Item 5792)
        - IS 88 Manhattan, tour by Sholem Levine, Israeli Union Leader, Apr 2, 1971 (Item 1449)
        - IS 88 Brooklyn, VOTE/COPE, Feb 1982 (Item 5521)
        - IS 88 Brooklyn, Sol Levine Visits, Feb 1982 (Item 5521)
        - IS 88 Brooklyn, String Orchestra Performances at Various Schools, May 1982 (Item 5521)
        - IS 96 Brooklyn, arts fair, Aug 1972 (Item 1850)
        - IS 126, Lillian Gold's former co-workers Dan Sanders, George Altomare and Sol Levine help celebrate her birthday, Mar 1973 (Item 2610)
        - Shanker, Al speaking at IS 131 Bronx, Jan 11, 1971 (Item 161)
        - IS 131 Bronx, Al Shanker Speaking, Jan 11, 1971 (Item 1351)
        - IS 131 Bronx, visiting "Eye-Opener" travelling show sponsored by the Metropolitan Museum of Art, Mar 1971 (Item 1497)
        - IS 137 Bronx, undated (Item 4787)
        - IS 144 Bronx, Dec 1979 (Item 5223)
        - IS 144 Bronx, School Conditions, Mar 1980 (Item 5223)
        - IS 145 Queens, mini-school opening, May 1972 (Item 2689)
        - CIS [Cities in Schools?] 148 Bronx, "Community Speak Out program," 1/23, undated (Item 2194)
        - IS 151 Bronx, Michael Gene, NY Yankees, Jan 1980 (Item 5223)
        - IS 154 Bronx, Martin Luther King Jr. Day celebration, Jan 1971 (Item 1287)
        - IS 162 Bronx, opening ceremonies, Apr 23, 1971 (Item 1468)
        - IS 162 Bronx, mini-school, Jun 1973 (Item 2639)
        - IS 162 Bronx, Oct 1973 (Item 2719)
        - Levine, Bob (IS 166, Bronx), undated (Item 5628)
        - IS 167, undated (Item 5782)
        - IS 181 Bronx, Library Media Center, May 1975 (Item 3739)
        - IS 201, building shots, 1967 (Item 259)
        - Marsh, John of 201 speaking to reporter, undated (Item 250)
        - IS 201, Lisser at a press conference, Lisser speaking to students, undated (Item 150)
        - IS 210 Brooklyn, demonstration for new mini-school, Nov 9, 1970 (Item 1211)
        - IS 218, scholarship awards presentation, Jun 24, 1971 (Item 1683)
        - IS 218 Brooklyn, Black History Exhibit, undated (Item 1853)
        - IS 227 Brooklyn, Eugene Putterman, undated (Item 5104)
        - Mark Twain JHS [IS 239], undated (Item 4799)
        - Picketing Walt Whitman IS [246], undated (Item 170)